https://www.kelley-ross.com/privacy-statement/

206.838.4567
Email
Privacy Statement
Kelley-Ross Pharmacy GroupPrivacy Statement
Please click here for our complete HIPAA Notice of Privacy Practices for Patients of Kelley-Ross.
Kelley-Ross is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Kelley-Ross Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Kelley-Ross website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Kelley-Ross collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Kelley-Ross also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Kelley-Ross. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Kelley-Ross for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Kelley-Ross Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Kelley-Ross public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Kelley-Ross does not read any of your private online communications.
Kelley-Ross encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Kelley-Ross so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Kelley-Ross is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Kelley-Ross and Kelley-Ross family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Kelley-Ross collects and uses your personal information to operate the Kelley-Ross Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Kelley-Ross also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Kelley-Ross and its affiliates. Kelley-Ross may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Kelley-Ross does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Kelley-Ross may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Kelley-Ross may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Kelley-Ross, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Kelley-Ross does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Kelley-Ross keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Kelley-Ross, in order to determine what Kelley-Ross services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Kelley-Ross to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Kelley-Ross Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Kelley-Ross or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Kelley-Ross; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Kelley-Ross, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Kelley-Ross Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Kelley-Ross pages, or register with Kelley-Ross site or services, a cookie helps Kelley-Ross to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Kelley-Ross Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Kelley-Ross features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Kelley-Ross services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Kelley-Ross secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Kelley-Ross secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Kelley-Ross will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Kelley-Ross encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Kelley-Ross is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Kelley-Ross welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Kelley-Ross has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Kelley-Ross at info@kelley-ross.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
About Kelley-RossHome Page
About Us
Kelley-Ross Pharmacy History
Team Manifesto
Leadership Team
Pharmacy Careers
Ask The Pharmacist
Contact Kelley-Ross Pharmacy Group
Employees/Patients
Strip Packaging (Automated Pill Box)
Union Center New Patient Form
Refill A Prescription
Union Center Pharmacy FAQs
Contact
The Polyclinic PharmacyOne-Step PrEP®
One-Step PEP™
Concierge Travel Clinic
Naloxone Program
Strip Packaging (Automated Pill Box)
Medisync Cycle Fill Program
Immunizations & Vaccinations
Tuberculosis (TB) Screening
Refill Prescription
Polyclinic FAQ
Contact Polyclinic
Make a Payment
CompoundingPrescribers
Refill a Prescription
Clinical Pharmacy InstituteCommunity Pharmacy Residency Program (CPRP)
CPRP Application Process
Frequently Asked Questions
Health and Housing
In-Home Medication Coaching
Contact
Naloxone ProgramNaloxone Provider Toolkit: FAQ
Naloxone Patient Toolkit: FAQ
Contact Naloxone Program
Quick Links and FormsInformation Sheet
General UCP order form
Auto Refill Authorization
Yearly Patient Update Form
Easy Open-Order Form
Make a Payment
Kelley-Ross has been Seattle’s resource for innovative pharmacy services since 1925. We provide PCAB accredited compounding, ACHC accredited specialty pharmacy, innovative medication management, customized Long Term Care solutions and more.
© Kelley-Ross & Associates, Inc. All rights reserved. Design by Rhombus
Privacy Statement
Terms of Use
Home
About
Long-Term Care Pharmacy
Union Center
Polyclinic
Compounding Pharmacy
Employees/Patients
Strip Packaging (Automated Pill Box)
Union Center New Patient Form
Refill A Prescription
FAQ
Contact
Polyclinic Pharmacy
One-Step PrEP®
One-Step PEP™
Concierge Travel Clinic
Naloxone Program
Strip Packaging (Automated Pill Box)
Medisync Cycle Fill Program
Immunizations & Vaccinations
Tuberculosis (TB) Screening
Refill Prescription
Polyclinic FAQ
Contact Polyclinic
Compounding Pharmacy
Prescribers
Ask The Pharmacist
Kelley-Ross is an independently owned corporation operating 4 pharmacies in Seattle. Kelley-Ross provides a wide range of pharmacy services, including prescription dispensing, compounding, medi-set packaging, compliance packaging, long-term care facility services, consultant pharmacist services, immunizations and a variety of health screenings.
We provide Clinical Community Care. This means that our staff combines expert medication therapy management and clinical skills, with caring, patient centered pharmacy services. By using the triad approach – patient, provider and pharmacist – we can help patients maximize their healthcare resources while achieving optimal health outcomes.
Our high service level and commitment to problem solving has made Kelley-Ross the pharmacy of choice for patients and providers across the Northwest.
